Nkenganang Cletus Fochap

Email: <u>nkencletus@gmail.com</u>

Tel: +4571659509

Address : Fansavej 31 C, 3 4600, Koge Denmark

Summary

I am a Full Stack Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in web programming languages including HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Reacts, NordJs, Express Js, MySQL. I also have a strong background in System administration, Technical support and Teaching.

Technical Skills

- Windows/Linus Systems
- HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript
- ReactJS, NodeJs, ExpressJs, Bootstrap
- MySQL, SQL, Postgres
- Technical Support

- Package Manager NPM
- GIT BASH/ GIT/GITHUB
- WEBPACK
- Wordpress
- Teaching

Languages

English: Professional LevelFrench: Professional Level

• Danish: Basic

Education

Master of Science: Information Technology, Information Science – June 2016

Aalborg University, Denmark.

Bachelors Diploma: DIPET I Computer Engineering - July 2010

Douala University, Cameroon

Experience

Full Stack Web Development: Freelance June 2017 - present

Computer Science Teacher (Web development / Management of Information Systems) :

December 2010 - September 2014

Lycee Technique de Bafoussam, Cameroon

• Preparing high School students for Technical baccalaureate examination.

System administrator/IT technical Support: December 2010 – September 2014 Multimedia Lab Lycee technique de Bafoussam

- Install, upgrade and monitor software and hardware in the mulitmedia lab
- Provide technical support to Staffs
- Troubleshoot incidents related to desktops and laptops, Windows servers as well as the network in the lab.

Certifications

Full Stack Web Developer: No Expiration Time (good for life)

Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate MCSA 2016: In progress

Redhat Certified System Administration: In progress